<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="crypt_keeper_encrypt_summary">Password required to decrypt device each time you turn it on.</string>
    <string name="crypt_keeper_desc">"You can encrypt accounts, settings, downloaded applications, and their data, media, and other files. Once you encrypt your device, a password will be required to decrypt it each time you power it on.

Encryption takes an hour or more. Start with a charged battery and keep device plugged in until encryption is completed. Interrupting may cause you to lose some or all data."</string>
    <string name="unlock_set_unlock_disabled_summary">Disabled by administrator, encryption policy, or credential storage.</string>
    <string name="manage_device_admin_summary">View or disable device administrators.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_empty_list_bluetooth_off">To see devices, turn on Bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="wifi_ap_allowed_list_empty">Tap the button at the top of the screen to add devices to the allowed device list.</string>
    <string name="wifi_ap_instruction_battery_warning">Mobile Hotspot consumes more battery. Connect the device to an outlet to extend battery life.</string>
    <string name="wifi_ap_instruction_changeable_maxclient_mid">You can create an allowed device list and set the connection mode for allowed devices.</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_settings_summary">Set up peer-to-peer connectivity.</string>
    <string name="dtmf_tone_enable_summary_on">Play tones when keypad is pressed.</string>
    <string name="dtmf_tone_enable_summary_off">Play tones when keypad is pressed.</string>
    <string name="sound_effects_enable_summary_on">Play sound when making screen selection.</string>
    <string name="sound_effects_enable_summary_off">Play sound when making screen selection.</string>
    <string name="lock_sounds_enable_summary_on">Play sounds when locking and unlocking screen.</string>
    <string name="lock_sounds_enable_summary_off">Play sounds when locking and unlocking screen.</string>
    <string name="dock_sounds_enable_summary_on">Play sounds when inserting and removing device from dock.</string>
    <string name="device_status_summary">Show status of battery, network, and other information.</string>
    <string name="master_clear_summary">Reset all settings and delete all data on device.</string>
    <string name="master_clear_desc">All data will be erased from USB storage, including your Google account, system and application data, settings, and downloaded applications.</string>
    <string name="install_unknown_applications">Allow installation of non-Market apps.</string>
    <string name="user_dict_settings_empty_text">No words in user dictionary. Add a word by tapping the add (+) button.</string>
    <string name="enable_adb_summary">Debugging mode launches when USB is connected.</string>
    <string name="allow_mock_location">Allow mock locations.</string>
    <string name="allow_mock_location_summary">Allow mock locations.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_long_press_timeout_title">Press and hold delay</string>
    <string name="tts_default_rate_summary">Speed at which the text is spoken.</string>
    <string name="tts_play_example_summary">Play short demonstration of speech synthesis.</string>
    <string name="vpn_settings_summary">Set up and manage Virtual Private Networks (VPNs).</string>
    <string name="credentials_install_summary">Install certificates from storage.</string>
    <string name="credentials_reset_summary">Remove all certificates.</string>
    <string name="trusted_credentials_summary">Display trusted CA certificates.</string>
    <string name="credentials_configure_lock_screen_hint">Set a screen unlock pattern, PIN, or password before you using credential storage.</string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary">Back up app data, Wi-Fi passwords, and other settings to Google servers.</string>
    <string name="auto_restore_summary">When reinstalling an application, backed up settings and data will be restored.</string>
    <string name="local_backup_password_summary_none">Full desktop backups are not currently protected.</string>
    <string name="no_device_admins">No device administrators available.</string>
    <string name="strict_mode_summary">Make screen flash when apps perform long operations on main thread.</string>
    <string name="pointer_location_summary">Screen overlay showing current touch data.</string>
    <string name="show_touches_summary">Show visual feedback for touch interactions.</string>
    <string name="show_screen_updates_summary">Make areas of screen flash when they update.</string>
    <string name="show_cpu_usage_summary">Screen overlay showing current CPU usage.</string>
    <string name="force_hw_ui_summary">Use 2D hardware acceleration in applications.</string>
    <string name="immediately_destroy_activities_summary">Destroy every activity as soon as the user leaves it.</string>
    <string name="show_all_anrs_summary">Show app not responding dialogue for background apps.</string>
    <string name="data_usage_empty">No apps used data during this time.</string>
    <string name="driving_mode_summary">Incoming calls and new notifications will be read out automatically.</string>
    <string name="desk_cradle_summary">Use external speakers when device is docked.</string>
    <string name="touch_key_light_summary">Adjust the delay before the Touch key light automatically turns off.</string>
    <string name="clock_summary">Show clock on lock screen.</string>
    <string name="help_text_summary">Show help text on lock screen.</string>
    <string name="encrypt_tablet_require_password">Set an unlock password of at least 6 characters, containing at least 1 number.</string>
    <string name="power_saving_tips_cpu">This option limits the maximum CPU performance and helps to conserve battery life. It will not effect normal usage, like browsing and video playback, if you do not use resource-intensive apps and games.</string>
    <string name="power_saving_tips_display">This option reduces the screen frame rate and lowers the brightness. It helps to extend battery life when the screen is turned on.</string>
    <string name="high_contrast_summary">Reverses the colors of screen.</string>
    <string name="power_key_hold_summary">Press and hold the power key to use the accessibility shortcut under device options.</string>
    <string name="mono_audio_summary">Provides mono audio for listening with one earphone.</string>
    <string name="tilt_tutorial_content">Press and hold at two points, then tilt device back and forth to zoom in or out of screen</string>
    <string name="motion_camera_short_cut_summary">Press and hold the screen while rotating the device to open Camera</string>
    <string name="learn_about_rotate_content">Holding the device straight, press and hold the screen and rotate the device to open Camera</string>
    <string name="dualclock_settings_summary">Show dual clock on lock screen when roaming.</string>
    <string name="display_battery_percentage_summary">Shows battery percentage on indicator.</string>
    <string name="led_indicator_charging_summary">LED lights up when device is connected to charger. LED will only light up when screen is off.</string>
    <string name="led_indicator_missed_event_summary">LED lights up when you have missed calls, messages, or application events. LED will only light up when screen is off.</string>
    <string name="desk_home_screen_display_summary">Show desk home screen when device is docked.</string>
    <string name="location_e911_description">E911 Location cannot be turned off on any mobile cellular phone.</string>
    <string name="location_vzw_description">Use location services provided by Verizon Wireless.</string>
    <string name="location_3rdparty_gps_description">Use location services based on Standalone GPS.</string>
    <string name="location_3rdparty_network_description">Use location services provided by Google.</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_shortcut_summary">Set shortcuts on lock screen.</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_shortcut_guide_title">Set shortcuts on lock screen.</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_shortcut_guide_content_2">Drag and drop to delete or change order.</string>
    <string name="voice_input_control_summry">Use voice commands to control device.</string>
    <string name="voice_input_control_incomming_calls_summary">You can answer or reject calls with the voice commands %1$s and %2$s. Speaker will turn on when you answer a call using voice command.</string>
    <string name="voice_input_control_alarm_summary">You can stop or snooze alarms with the voice commands %1$s and %2$s.</string>
    <string name="voice_input_control_camera_summary">You can take pictures with voice commands like %1$s, %2$s, %3$s, and %4$s.</string>
    <string name="voice_input_control_music_summary">You can control the music player with the voice commands %1$s, %2$s, %3$s, %4$s, %5$s, and %6$s.</string>
    <string name="notify_me_available_network_summary">When launching high data usage applications (Wi-Fi ON), scan for nearby Wi-Fi networks and notify me when available.</string>
    <string name="wifi_connect_seamlessly_summary">When launching high data usage applications, connect to known Wi-Fi networks when Wi-Fi is off.</string>
    <string name="all_sound_off_summary">Turn off all sounds including receiver voice.</string>
    <string name="led_indicator_low_battery_summary">LED lights up when battery level is low. LED will only light up when screen is off.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_speak_password_summary">When explore by touch is enabled, characters entered in password fields are read out by the device.</string>
    <string name="wakeup_in_lockscreen_summary">Unlock using wake-up command when swipe or motion lock enabled.</string>
    <string name="audio_applications_summary">Connecting earphones will enable audio applications in quick panel.</string>
</resources>
